export const physics = [
  {
    choices: ["reaction", "scalar", "resultant", "tensor"],
    correctAnswer: "resultant",
    question: "what is the name of a vector that represents the sum of two vectors?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["0.8", "62.4", "1000", "1.0"],
    correctAnswer: "1.0",
    question: "what is the specific gravity of water?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["force", "power", "work", "energy"],
    correctAnswer: "force",
    question: "newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law of motion states that the rate of change of momentum with respect to time is ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["hooke&amp;amp;#39;s law of equilibrium", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law of motion", "faraday&amp;amp;#39;s law of forces", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s first law of motion"],
    correctAnswer: "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law of motion",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot;whenever a net force acts on a body, it produces an acceleration in the direction of the resultant force, an acceleration that is directly proportional to the mass of the body. this theory is popularly known as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Q=-mLv", "Q=-mLf", "Q=mLv", "Q=mLf"],
    correctAnswer: "Q=-mLf",
    question: "in physics, if Lf and Lv are the latent heat of fusion and vaporization, respectively, which of the following equations apply in determining the amount of energy needed to freeze a liquid?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["elastic potential energy", "heat energy", "rest energy", "thermal energy"],
    correctAnswer: "thermal energy",
    question: "The kinetic energy of the atoms and molecules due to their randome motion is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Erg", "Joule", "Slug", "Dyne"],
    correctAnswer: "Slug",
    question: "The mass to which a force of one pound will give an acceleration of one foot per second per second.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["970 BTU/lbm", "334 kJ/kg", "2256 kJ/kg", "168 BTU/lbm"],
    correctAnswer: "334 kJ/kg",
    question: "what is the latent heat fusion required to turn ice to liquid?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Joule", "watt", "kilowatt-hour", "horsepower"],
    correctAnswer: "watt",
    question: "What is the SI unit of power?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["negative value", "1", "infinity", "0"],
    correctAnswer: "1",
    question: "for perfect elastic collision, the coefficient of restitution, e is equal to",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["hydraulic theorem", "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "pascal&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "ideal fluid theorem"],
    correctAnswer: "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s theorem",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot; at any two points along a streamline in an ideal fluid in a steady flow, the sum of the pressure, the potential energy per unit volume and the kinetic energy per unit volume has the same value&amp;amp;#39;. this concepts is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["impact", "momentum", "coefficient of restitution", "impulse"],
    correctAnswer: "impulse",
    question: "The product of a force and the time during which it acts is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["4 C", "100 C", "373 K", "273 K"],
    correctAnswer: "273 K",
    question: "melting point of ice is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Displacement", "Impulse", "Energy", "Momentum"],
    correctAnswer: "Momentum",
    question: "A vector quantity which is a product of mass and velocity of the body.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["N-s", "kg-m/s", "N-m/s", "Slugs/s"],
    correctAnswer: "N-s",
    question: "What is the SI unit of Impulse?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["kinetic energy", "impulse", "momentum", "acceleration"],
    correctAnswer: "momentum",
    question: "if the velocity of the body doubled in value, its ______ will also doubled.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["erg", "joule", "Btu", "watt"],
    correctAnswer: "joule",
    question: "The work done by a force of 1 newton acting through a distance of 1m is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["initial velocity and weight of the body", "initial velocity and angle of prejection", "initial velocity only", "initial velocity, weight of the body of the angle of projection"],
    correctAnswer: "initial velocity and angle of prejection",
    question: "the range of projectile depends on",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["energy", "momentum", "work", "power"],
    correctAnswer: "work",
    question: "The product of force and displacement is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific gravity", "temperature", "density", "velocity"],
    correctAnswer: "temperature",
    question: "absolute viscosity is essentially independent of pressure and is primarily dependent on",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["atoms and molecules", "masses", "atoms", "molecules"],
    correctAnswer: "atoms and molecules",
    question: "Thermal energy refers to the random kinetic energy of all ________ in a substance.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Newton", "Pound", "Erg", "Dyne"],
    correctAnswer: "Erg",
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a unit of force?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["law of universal gravitation", "newton&amp;amp;#39;s law of motion", "kepler&amp;amp;#39;s law", "big bang and black hole theory"],
    correctAnswer: "kepler&amp;amp;#39;s law",
    question: "the law which describes the motion of stars, planets and comets",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["newton&amp;amp;#39;s law", "inverse square law", "law of universal gravitational", "coulumb&amp;amp;#39;s law"],
    correctAnswer: "coulumb&amp;amp;#39;s law",
    question: "according to this law &amp;amp;quot;the force between two charges varies directly as the magnitude of each charge and inversely as the square of the distance between them&amp;amp;quot;",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["motion and weight", "mass and acceleration", "motion and mass", "weight and velocity"],
    correctAnswer: "motion and mass",
    question: "momentum is a property related to the object&amp;amp;#39;s ______.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Joule", "Dyne", "Slug", "Newton"],
    correctAnswer: "Dyne",
    question: "The unit of force which is equivalent to 1 gram-cm/sec^2",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["archimides principle", "venturi&amp;amp;#39;s principle", "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "pascal&amp;amp;#39;s law"],
    correctAnswer: "archimides principle",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot;any body immersed in a fluid is subjected to a bouyant force which is equal to the weight of the fluid displaced&amp;amp;quot; this is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["internal energy", "elastic potential energy", "kinetic energy", "mechanical energy"],
    correctAnswer: "elastic potential energy",
    question: "the energy stored in a stretched elastic material such as a spring is ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["all vector quantities have magnitudes", "all scalar quantities have magnitudes", "all scalar quantities have directions", "all vector quantities have directions"],
    correctAnswer: "all scalar quantities have directions",
    question: "which of the following is incorret?&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["teh distance between the neutral axis to the outermost fiber", "einstein constant", "speed of sound", "speed of light"],
    correctAnswer: "speed of light",
    question: "in the equation E = mc^2, c is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["when their masses are equal to the target is stationary", "when the target is stationary even if their masses are not equal", "when their masses are equal and the target is moving with a speed greater than that of the colliding body", "when their masses are equal and the target is moving with a speed less than that of the colliding body"],
    correctAnswer: "when their masses are equal to the target is stationary",
    question: "at what situation when the colliding objects stops and the target moves off with same speed after collision?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Speed", "Motion", "Velocity", "Acceleration"],
    correctAnswer: "Velocity",
    question: "The displacement per unit time.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["force", "velocity", "acceleration", "time"],
    correctAnswer: "velocity",
    question: "momentum is the product of mass and",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["total potential energy", "total momentum", "total impulse", "total mechanical energy"],
    correctAnswer: "total mechanical energy",
    question: "The work done by all forces except the gravitational force is always equal to the ____ of the system.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["7.5", "13.6", "0.8", "1.0"],
    correctAnswer: "13.6",
    question: "what is the specific gravity of mercury?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["ductility", "malleability", "plasticity", "elasticity"],
    correctAnswer: "elasticity",
    question: "the property by virtue of which a body tends to return to its original size of shape after deformation and when deformation forces have been removed.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["1 torr", "barometric pressure", "gauge pressure", "all of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "gauge pressure",
    question: "the difference between the absolute pressure and the atmospheric pressure is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific gravity of fluid x volume submerged", "density of fluid x volume above the surface", "density of fluid x volume submerged", "density of fluid x total volume"],
    correctAnswer: "density of fluid x volume submerged",
    question: "bouyant force is equal to",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["fluid theorem", "pascal&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s energy theorem", "hydraulic theorem"],
    correctAnswer: "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s energy theorem",
    question: "any two points along the streamline in an ideal fluid is steady state flow, the sum of pressire, the potential energy per unit volume and the kinetic energy per unit volume has the same value. this concept is know as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["momentum", "power", "energy", "impulse"],
    correctAnswer: "energy",
    question: "The capacity to do work is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["decceleration", "speed", "acceleration", "velocity"],
    correctAnswer: "acceleration",
    question: "a free falling body is a body in a rectilinear motion and with contant _______",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["fall to the ground", "is moved vertically upward", "all of the above", "is moved parallel to the surface of the earth"],
    correctAnswer: "is moved parallel to the surface of the earth",
    question: "The force due to gravity does not work on objects that",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["water manometer", "metallic diaphragm", "mercury manometer", "bourdon"],
    correctAnswer: "mercury manometer",
    question: "what is the gage used to measure 0.001 to 1 atm pressure?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["cold fusion", "latent heat of fusion", "solid fusion", "condensation"],
    correctAnswer: "latent heat of fusion",
    question: "the amount of heat needed to change solid to liquid is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["horsepower", "watt", "Newton-meter/second", "joules"],
    correctAnswer: "joules",
    question: "All are units of power except",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["absolute temperature scale is expressed in K", "absolute zero in fahrenheit scale is -273", "boiling point of centigrade scale is 100", "fahrenheit scale was invented by German"],
    correctAnswer: "boiling point of centigrade scale is 100",
    question: "indicate the false statement about temperature",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["length and sense", "length and direction", "direction and sense", "length, direction and sense"],
    correctAnswer: "length, direction and sense",
    question: "a vector is a straight line segment that has a definite",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific gravity", "density", "pressure", "specific weight "],
    correctAnswer: "specific gravity",
    question: "the ______ of substance is its density relative to that of pure water",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["mh/g", "mh", "mgh/2", "mgh"],
    correctAnswer: "mgh",
    question: "The work done in lifting an object of mass &amp;amp;quot;m&amp;amp;quot; to a height &amp;amp;quot;h&amp;amp;quot; is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["law of universal gravitation", "inverse-square law", "coulumb&amp;amp;#39;s law", "newton&amp;amp;#39;s law"],
    correctAnswer: "coulumb&amp;amp;#39;s law",
    question: "according to this law, &amp;amp;#39;the force between two charges varies directly  as the magnitude of each charge and inversely as the square of the distance between them&amp;amp;#39;.&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Moment of Inertia", "Force", "Acceleration", "Mass"],
    correctAnswer: "Mass",
    question: "A measure of inertia of a body, which is its resistance to a change in velocity.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["1.49", "2.19", "3.89", "4.19"],
    correctAnswer: "4.19",
    question: "what is the specific heat capacity of water in kJ/kg?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["2 C", "4 C", "100 C", "0 C"],
    correctAnswer: "100 C",
    question: "densed condition of water is at what temperature?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Coefficient of kinetic friction", "Ceefficient of restitution", "Coefficient of friction", "Coefficient of sliding"],
    correctAnswer: "Ceefficient of restitution",
    question: "The negative ration of the relative velocity after a collision to a relative velocity before a collision",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["newton&amp;amp;#39;s first law of motion", "faraday&amp;amp;#39;s law of force", "newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law of motion", "hooke&amp;amp;#39;s law"],
    correctAnswer: "newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law of motion",
    question: "whenever a net force acts on a body, it produces acceleration in the direction of the resultant force, an acceleration  which is directly proportional to the resultant force and inversely proportional to the mass of the body. this theory is known as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Elastic potential energy", "Gravitational potential energy", "Thermal energy", "Rest energy"],
    correctAnswer: "Gravitational potential energy",
    question: "The energy of an object due to its vertical separation from the earth&amp;amp;#39;s surface.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["acceleration", "velocity", "force", "time"],
    correctAnswer: "velocity",
    question: "Momentum is the product of mass and",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the colliding object continues its motion in the same direction the same speed", "colliding object continue its motion in the same direction with reduced speed", "the lighter the object bounces off the heavier one", "colliding object stops"],
    correctAnswer: "colliding object continue its motion in the same direction with reduced speed",
    question: "if the colliding object has a mass greater than that of the stationary target, after the impact, the",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["lift", "gravitational acceleration", "drag", "terminal speed"],
    correctAnswer: "terminal speed",
    question: "refers to the vertical speed at which the force of air resistance is just sufficient to balance the body&amp;amp;#39;s weight.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["kinetic energy", "displacement", "impulse", "power"],
    correctAnswer: "impulse",
    question: "Change of momentum is equal to ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["boyle&amp;amp;#39;s law", "torrecellos&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "archimedes principle"],
    correctAnswer: "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s theorem",
    question: "the sum of the pressure head, elevation head and velocity head remains constant. this known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["square of the area", "density of the fluid", "cube of the area", "square of the pressure head"],
    correctAnswer: "density of the fluid",
    question: "the total hydrostatic force on a plane are is directly proportinal to ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Weight of the body is always equal to its mass", "Weight of the body varies with its location", "Mass is the measure of the response of the body to an applied force.", "Weight of body is a gravitational force."],
    correctAnswer: "Weight of the body is always equal to its mass",
    question: "Indicate the FALSE statement.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Slugs/s", "kg-m/s", "N-m/s", "N-s"],
    correctAnswer: "N-s",
    question: "What is the SI unit of momentum?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["greater than that of the object thrown vertically downward", "zero until the object reaches maximum point", "is smaller than that of the object thrown vertically downward", "is equal to that of an object thrown vertically downward"],
    correctAnswer: "is equal to that of an object thrown vertically downward",
    question: "if an object is thrown vertically upward, its acceleration",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["barometer", "pitot tube", "wind vane", "thermometer"],
    correctAnswer: "barometer",
    question: "an instrument used to measure air pressure is the ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["law of inertia", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s first law", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s third law"],
    correctAnswer: "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s third law",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot;for every action, there is always an equal and opposite reaction&amp;amp;quot; this is known as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["convection", "conduction", "radiation", "conservation"],
    correctAnswer: "convection",
    question: "the transmission of heat from one place to another by fluid circulation between the spots of different temperature is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["focus", "perigee", "eccentricity", "apogee"],
    correctAnswer: "focus",
    question: "which of the following does not describe the object as observed from earth?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["center of gravity", "center of mass", "barycenter", "all of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "all of the above",
    question: "what is another term for centroid?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Speed", "Acceleration", "Velocity", "Motion"],
    correctAnswer: "Speed",
    question: "The distance per unit time.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["density", "weight", "volume", "mass"],
    correctAnswer: "mass",
    question: "A cart loaded with gravel is hard to get started rolling because of its large",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["-40", "-35", "-45", "-30"],
    correctAnswer: "-40",
    question: "at what temperature readings do the fahrenheit and celsius have the same value?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["rest energy", "thermal energy", "kinetic energy", "potential energy"],
    correctAnswer: "rest energy",
    question: "An energy by the virtue of the object&amp;amp;#39;s mass is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["equal", "less than", "equal to zero", "greater than"],
    correctAnswer: "less than",
    question: "inelastic collision is a collision in which the total kinetic energy after the collision is ___ before collision.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["output work to input work", "input distance to output distance", "power output to power input", "output force to input force"],
    correctAnswer: "output force to input force",
    question: "actual mechanical advantage is the ratio between:",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Inertia", "static", "equilibrium", "mass"],
    correctAnswer: "Inertia",
    question: "The tendency of any object to remain at rest or to continue in motion is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["impulse", "change in potential energy", "change in momentum", "change in kinetic energy"],
    correctAnswer: "change in kinetic energy",
    question: "The work done by the external force on particles is equal to the _____ of the practicle.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["cross product", "dot product ", "magnitude", "resultant"],
    correctAnswer: "dot product ",
    question: "the scalar product of two vectors are sometimes known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["equal to zero", "half the atmospheric pressure", "greater than zero", "less than zero"],
    correctAnswer: "equal to zero",
    question: " under normal condition, the gage pressure at water surface is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["directly propotional to the radius of the cutvature", "directly propotional to the square of the weight of the object", "inversely propotional to the square of the tangetial velocity", "directly propotional to the square of the tangential velocity"],
    correctAnswer: "directly propotional to the square of the tangential velocity",
    question: "centrifugal force ____",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["1gram/cc", "1000kg/m3", "9.82kN/m3", "62.4lb/ft3"],
    correctAnswer: "62.4lb/ft3",
    question: "which of the following is NOT a density of water?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["momentum", "inertia", "work", "power"],
    correctAnswer: "work",
    question: "Joules is an SI unit of",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["destructive interference always results", "the phase difference is always zero", "standing waves are produced", "constructive interference always results"],
    correctAnswer: "destructive interference always results",
    question: "when two waves of the same frequency, speed and the amplitude travelling in opposite directions superimposed.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["in completely  inelastic collision, no kinetic energy is lost", "kinetic energy is not conserved in an elastic collision", "in elastic collision, no energy is lost", "in elastic collision, the two colliding bodies stick together after impact"],
    correctAnswer: "in elastic collision, no energy is lost",
    question: "which of the following is true about collision?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific weight ", "mass", "density", "relative density"],
    correctAnswer: "relative density",
    question: "what is the another name for specific gravity?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["It is the same as the mass of the object.", "It is equivalent to the mass of the object divided by the gravitational acceleration", "It is the force with which it is attracted to the earth.", "It is constant anywhere in the universe."],
    correctAnswer: "It is the force with which it is attracted to the earth.",
    question: "Which of the following is true about the weight of an object?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["mass", "torque", "displacement", "electric field intensity"],
    correctAnswer: "mass",
    question: "all are vector quantities except",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["day", "hour ", "second", "minute "],
    correctAnswer: "second",
    question: "originally defined as the fraction 1/86400 of the mean solar day and now defines as the duration of 9, 192, 631, 770 periods of the radiation of a certain state of the cesium-133 atom",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the maximum height", "the speed", "all of the above", "the range of projectile"],
    correctAnswer: "all of the above",
    question: "in a trajectory, air resistance decreases",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the flower pot hits the ground first and with a higher speed  that the glass", "the flower pot and the glass hits the ground at the same time", "the flower pots hits the ground at the same time as the glass", "the glass hits the ground before the flower pot"],
    correctAnswer: "the flower pot hits the ground first and with a higher speed  that the glass",
    question: "a flower pot falls a ledge of a 5th floor window, just as it passes the third floor wondows,. someone accidentally drops a glass of water from the window. which of the following is true?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["0 C", "4 C", "32 F", "0 K"],
    correctAnswer: "0 K",
    question: "absolute zero temperature is ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["1 ton", "1 gram", "1 kilogram", "1 pound"],
    correctAnswer: "1 gram",
    question: "calorie is defined as the amount of heat required to raise a temperature of ____ of water 1 deg. celsius",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Quadrupled", "Remains the same", "Tripled", "Doubled"],
    correctAnswer: "Quadrupled",
    question: "What will happen to the kinetic energy of the body if its velocity doubled?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["all of the above", "the force is parallel to the displacement", "there is an angle between the force and the displacement", "the force is perpendicular to the displacement"],
    correctAnswer: "the force is perpendicular to the displacement",
    question: "There is no work done when",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific heat capacity", "BTU", "heat transfer", "temperature"],
    correctAnswer: "specific heat capacity",
    question: "the amount of heat needed to change the temperature of a unit quantity of it by 1 deg.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["speed", "energy", "temperature", "acceleration"],
    correctAnswer: "acceleration",
    question: "all are scalar quantities except",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the heat needed to raise the temperature of 1 gram of water 1 deg. fahrenheit", "a temperature of 1 kg sample reported in deg. celsius", "the energy needed to raise the temperature of 1 gram of a substance 1 deg. celsius", "any of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "the heat needed to raise the temperature of 1 gram of water 1 deg. fahrenheit",
    question: "what is specific heat?&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["The weight and mass of a body depends on its location.", "The weight of a body is independent on its location.", "The mass of the body is dependent on its location.", "The weight of a body depends on its location while the mass is independent of its location."],
    correctAnswer: "The weight of a body depends on its location while the mass is independent of its location.",
    question: "Which of the following statements is TRUE?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["1, 850, 763. 73", "1, 560, 763. 73", "1, 650, 763.73", "1, 750, 763.73"],
    correctAnswer: "1, 650, 763.73",
    question: "the standard meter defined as ____wavelengths in vacuum of the orange-red line of the spectrum of krypton86.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["all matter has mass", "the specific gravity of ivory soap is less than of water", "the density of ivory soap is unity", "the specific gravity of ivory soap is less than that of water"],
    correctAnswer: "the specific gravity of ivory soap is less than that of water",
    question: "ivory soap floats in water because",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the objects sticks together after impact", "the kinetic energy is not conserved", "the kinetic energy is conserved", "the loss of kinetic energy is maximum"],
    correctAnswer: "the kinetic energy is conserved",
    question: "in an elastic collision, ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["initial and final vertical position", "path followed in moving between two positions", "initial and final velocity", "all of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "initial and final vertical position",
    question: "The change in gravitational potential energy depends on the ______ of the object.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["inversely proportional to", "directly proportional to the square of", "inversely proportional to the square of", "directly proportional to"],
    correctAnswer: "directly proportional to",
    question: "the acceleration is ____ the resultant force on the object",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["mass x velocity", "1/2 mass x velocity^2", "mass x acceleration", "1/2 mass x velocity"],
    correctAnswer: "1/2 mass x velocity^2",
    question: "Kinetic energy equals",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["static collision", "plastic collision", "elastic collision", "inelastic collision"],
    correctAnswer: "elastic collision",
    question: "when the total kinetic energy of the system is the same as before and after collision of two bodies, it is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["23.3ft/s2", "980ft/s2", "32.2 ft/s2", "9.81ft/s2"],
    correctAnswer: "32.2 ft/s2",
    question: "the standard acceleration due to gravity is ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["gamma radiation", "transmission radiation", "walton radiation", "betatron radiation"],
    correctAnswer: "gamma radiation",
    question: "one of the types of non-material nuclear radiation is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific heat", "BTU", "heat of fusion", "heat of evaporation"],
    correctAnswer: "heat of evaporation",
    question: "the amount of heat must be supplied to change 1 kg of the substance at its boiling point from the liquid state to the gaseous state",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["archimedes principle", "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s theorem", "boyle&amp;amp;#39;s law", "pascal&amp;amp;#39;s law"],
    correctAnswer: "pascal&amp;amp;#39;s law",
    question: "if an exteral pressure is applied in a confined fluid, the pressure will be increased at every point in the fluid by the amount if external pressure. this is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["enthalpy", "internal energy", "entropy", "kinetic energy"],
    correctAnswer: "entropy",
    question: "is the measurement of randomness of the molecules of a substance",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["atmospheric pressure", "barometric pressure", "gauge pressure", "gauge pressure + atmospheric pressure"],
    correctAnswer: "gauge pressure + atmospheric pressure",
    question: "absolute pressure equals",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the volume of ice will not change", "some parts of ice will not change", "ice will become water", "all of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "the volume of ice will not change",
    question: "one gram of ice at 0 degrees is place on a container containing 2,000,000 cubic meters of water at 0 degrees. assuming no heat loss, what will happen?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Inertia", "Either mass or weight", "Weight", "Mass"],
    correctAnswer: "Weight",
    question: "Defined as the gravitational force exerted on an object because of its attraction to some other masses such as the earth.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["luminous intensity", "luminance", "radiance", "illuminance"],
    correctAnswer: "illuminance",
    question: "it describes the luminous flux incidence per unit area and is primarily dependent on",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["flexibility", "ductility", "plasticity", "malleability"],
    correctAnswer: "plasticity",
    question: "_________  is the quality of being physically elongated.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["the weight of object", "the tangential velocity", "radius of curvature", "the square of the tangential velocity"],
    correctAnswer: "the square of the tangential velocity",
    question: "centrifugal force is directly proportional to",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["charle&amp;amp;#39;s law", "gay-lussac law", "ideal gas law", "boyle&amp;amp;#39;s law"],
    correctAnswer: "charle&amp;amp;#39;s law",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot; at constant pressure, the volume us directly proportional to temperature&amp;amp;quot; this is known as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Weight", "Specific weight", "Mass", "Relative density"],
    correctAnswer: "Mass",
    question: "Defined quantitatively as the amount of matter of which the object is made. It also refer to the measure of the object&amp;amp;#39;s inertia",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["newton", "kepler", "galileo", "varignon"],
    correctAnswer: "newton",
    question: "the accurate formuationof the laws of motions, as well as of gravitational was made by",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["compressibility", "shape elasticity", "volume stress", "volume strain"],
    correctAnswer: "volume strain",
    question: "the reciprocal of bulk modulus of any fluid is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Acceleration", "Weight ", "Force", "Mass"],
    correctAnswer: "Mass",
    question: "A quantitative measure of inertia.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["is in equilibrium", "in motion", "is subjected to friction", "subjected to a force"],
    correctAnswer: "in motion",
    question: "Kinetic means that it is ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Slug", "Erg", "Kilowatt-hour", "Joules"],
    correctAnswer: "Slug",
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a unit or work?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["N-cm", "kg-m", "Joule", "Foot-pound"],
    correctAnswer: "Joule",
    question: "What is the SI unit of work?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["pascal&amp;amp;#39;s principle", "ideal fluid principle", "bernoulli&amp;amp;#39;s princple", "archimedes  principle"],
    correctAnswer: "pascal&amp;amp;#39;s principle",
    question: "the fluid pressure is the same in all directions. this is known as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["ideal gas law", "charle&amp;amp;#39;s law", "boyle&amp;amp;#39;s law", "gay-lussac law"],
    correctAnswer: "boyle&amp;amp;#39;s law",
    question: "at constant temperature, the volume is inversely proportional to the pressure&amp;amp;quot; this is know as ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["due to the presence of the potential energy", "due to the presence of friction", "due to its efficiency", "due to its speed"],
    correctAnswer: "due to the presence of friction",
    question: "Why it is that the power delivered by any machine is always less than the power supplies to it?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Newton&amp;amp;#39;s first law", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s third law", "kepler&amp;amp;#39;s law", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law"],
    correctAnswer: "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s first law",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot; every body continues units state of rest or at constant speed in a straight line motion, it is compelled to change that state because of forces acting on it&amp;amp;quot;, this is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["specific gravity", "inertia", "malleability", "specific weight"],
    correctAnswer: "specific weight",
    question: "what is another term for density?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["positive ", "zero", "positive or negative", "negative"],
    correctAnswer: "zero",
    question: "what is the value of the work done for a closed reversible, isometric system. ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["ellipse", "hyperbola", "parabola", "circle"],
    correctAnswer: "parabola",
    question: "the trajectory of projectile is a graph of",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["calorie", "thermal energy", "british thermal unit (BTU)", "specific heat"],
    correctAnswer: "british thermal unit (BTU)",
    question: "the amount of heat required to change the temperature1 pound of water 1 deg. fahrenheit",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["barycenter", "centroid", "center of gravity", "all of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "all of the above",
    question: "a point on the object from which it can be suspended in any orientation without tending to rotate",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["colliding object stops", "the lighter object bounces off the heavier one", "the colliding object continues its motion in the same direction with reduced speed ", "the colliding object continues its motion in the same direction with the same speed"],
    correctAnswer: "the lighter object bounces off the heavier one",
    question: "if the colliding object has a mass less than that of the stationary target, after the impact, the",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["7460 watts", "746 watts", "7.46 watts", "74.6 watts"],
    correctAnswer: "746 watts",
    question: "one horsepower is equivalent to ",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["destructive interference always results", "the phase difference is always zero", "constructive interference always results", "standing waves are produces"],
    correctAnswer: "destructive interference always results",
    question: "when two waves of the same frequency, speed and apmlitude travelling in opposite directions are superimposed.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Force", "Momentum", "Energy", "Power"],
    correctAnswer: "Power",
    question: "The rate of doing work.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Inelastic collision", "Off center collision", "Elastic collision", "Straight line collision"],
    correctAnswer: "Inelastic collision",
    question: "A collision in which the total kinetic energy after collision is less than that before collision.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["R = (V^2/g)sin2theta", "R = (2Vsintheta)/g", "R = (2V sintheta)/g", "R = (V/g)sin2theta"],
    correctAnswer: "R = (V^2/g)sin2theta",
    question: "in the absence of air resistance, a projectile sent off at an angle of theta above the horizontal with an initial velocity of V has a horizontal range of",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["latent heat ", "calorie", "BTU", "specific heat"],
    correctAnswer: "BTU",
    question: "the amount of heat needed to raise the temperature of one pound of that substance one degree fahrenheit is",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["viscosity of the fluid", "gravity", "air resistance", "surface tension"],
    correctAnswer: "surface tension",
    question: "a leak from a faucet comes out in separate drops. which of the following is the main cause of this phenomenon?",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["force, velocity, time", "force. time", "force, displacement", "force, acceleration, time"],
    correctAnswer: "force. time",
    question: "linear momentum is the product of mass and velocity and this can be expressed as a function of",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["velocity", "acceleration", "Force", "vector"],
    correctAnswer: "Force",
    question: "Any influence capable of producing change in the motion of an object is called",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["moment of inertia", "friction", "torsion", "angular acceleration"],
    correctAnswer: "angular acceleration",
    question: "a measure of resistance of a body it offers to any changes in its angular velocity, determined by its mass and distribution of its mass about the axis of rotation is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["relative weight", "specific gravity", "specific weight", "mass"],
    correctAnswer: "specific gravity",
    question: "the ratio of the density of the substance to the density of water",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Work = force x distance", "The unit of work in the SI system is joules and erg in the English system", "Work is a scalar quantity.", "Work = power x time"],
    correctAnswer: "The unit of work in the SI system is joules and erg in the English system",
    question: "Indicate the false statement about work.",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["viscosity", "laminar flow", "surface tension", "capillarity"],
    correctAnswer: "viscosity",
    question: "refers to the fluid&amp;amp;#39;s internal friction",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["heat of fusion", "heat of evaporation", "BTU", "specific heat"],
    correctAnswer: "heat of fusion",
    question: "the amount of heat must be supplied to change 1 kg of the substance at its melting point from the solid to the liquid state",
    topic: "NA"
  },
  {
    choices: ["Newton&amp;amp;#39;s first law", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law", "Kepler&amp;amp;#39;s law", "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s third law"],
    correctAnswer: "Newton&amp;amp;#39;s second law",
    question: "&amp;amp;quot; an unbalanced force acting on an object will cause the object to accelerate in the direction of the force&amp;amp;quot;. this is known as",
    topic: "NA"
  },
]